Over half of American TV viewers now use subtitles whenever they watch TV, according to survey company YouGov.
根据调查公司YouGov的数据，超过一半的美国电视观众现在看电视时都会使用字幕。
This trend is even more noticeable in viewers under 30.
这种趋势在30岁以下的观众中更为明显。
Subtitles have long been used to help people with hearing impairments or to allow people to watch films in a different language, but why has their use become so widespread?
长期以来，字幕一直用于帮助有听力障碍的人，或者让人们观看不同语言的电影，但为什么字幕的使用变得如此普遍呢？
The reasons for this are both technical and social.
其原因既有技术方面的，也有社会方面的。
Advances in digital sound production and microphones mean that actors can be more natural in their vocal performance, while at the same time audio directors are able to make more and more dramatic soundscapes.
数字声音制作和麦克风的进步意味着演员可以更自然地进行声音表演，同时音频导演能够制作出越来越戏剧化的声景。
Combined with the much smaller speakers contained in modern TV sets, this can all make dialogue seem unintelligible.
再加上现代电视机中内置的扬声器尺寸小得多，所有这些都可能导致对话听起来难以理解。
Smartphones may play a role.
智能手机可能也起到了一定作用。
We are used to subtitled social media videos that can be watched without headphones.
我们已经习惯了无需耳机即可观看的带字幕的社交媒体视频。
Smartphones also allow us to watch film and TV in public places where they are not easily audible.
智能手机还让我们可以在公共场所观看电影和电视节目，而在这些地方声音不易听清。
Another social reason could be the increased appetite for programmes in other languages accessible through international streaming services.
另一个社会原因可能是，通过国际流媒体服务可以获取的其他语言的节目需求增加了。
While some viewers may consider subtitles to be distracting, or worry about the potential for spoilers, they don't just help with unclear audio.
虽然有些观众可能认为字幕会分散注意力，或者担心有剧透的可能，但字幕不仅仅有助于解决音频不清楚的问题。
A number of studies have suggested that subtitles could help people to increase their vocabulary and boost their listening skills in languages that they do not currently speak.
许多研究表明，字幕可以帮助人们增加词汇量，并提高他们目前不熟悉语言的听力技能。
This may be particularly effective when subtitles are in the same language as the audio track of the programme.
当字幕与节目的音轨使用同一种语言时，这可能尤其有效。
Same-language subtitles have also been shown to help young children develop their reading skills in their first language, to the point where campaigners have suggested enabling subtitles on all children's programmes by default.
同语言字幕也被证明有助于幼儿发展他们的母语阅读能力，以至于支持者们建议在所有儿童节目中默认开启字幕。